A T F. Chicago is responding to this active
shooter situation. The locals are now reporting that as
well. And I want to give you Mohr.
You heard the local anchor there mentioned, uh,
suburban newspaper there for the suburbs of Chicago Is the
Daily Herald on it is the one who's on scene
and reporting that four Aurora police officers and multiple civilians
have been shot. We've been saying injured because that
was all the information we had. Now, this
is the first hard report from from the locals that
people have actually been shot. And among those four
Aurora police officers and multiple civilians shot with a with
a the suspect at large again. That's from the
Daily Herald, which bills itself Suburban Chicago's information source
. And I'll give you the rest that they have
reading through now from The Daily Herald. Four areas
for Aurora, Illinois police officers, multiple civilians have
been wounded, and the suspect suspected shooter is still
at large in this industrial area near Prairie and Highlands
Avenue, according to preliminary reports from the scene.
There were unconfirmed reports earlier, which I won't get
into because they're unconfirmed, but I can tell you
multiple victims are now being airlifted. Toe advocate Good
Samaritan Hospital in Downers Grove, which is nearby again
. This the reporting of the Daily Herald SWAT teams
from through throughout the suburbs are being called to the
scene. Police are urging anyone in this area to
shelter in place and nearby Holy Angels school, and
some businesses are on what you heard earlier as a
soft locked down. So what was a serious situation
has become much more dire now, with the reporting
now from the from the suburban newspaper that four Aurora
police officers and multiple civilians have been shot and the
suspect currently at large. Ah, Jonathan Hunt is
work. Our chief correspondent is working sources in the
background here for some updates. Jonathan, what are
you learning, Shep? I think it's important to
note here that this is clearly a very active scene
. Still, obviously, the school district is a
major concern here. The West Aurora School District one
to nine has already posted a message to all parents
saying that every single district student is being held in
place now. Ah, locked down at all schools
. And the major concern, of course, is
that there is no indication what so ever at this
point that the police know exactly where this shooter is
that we certainly have no reports of anybody taken into
custody at this point on, I think, is
you look at these aerial pictures ship Shep around the
Henry Pratt Building in Aurora. It's interesting to note
, and I have not seen. I'm not sure
if you have, but I have not seen many